(ELEVATOR DINGS)
(HIGH HEELS CLACKING)
Mr. Director,
this is Agent Vivian Delay.
For the last ten years,
the CentraI Intelligence Agency
- has been after Wolfgang Braun.
- The Wolf.
As you know, we have no positive
identification on what the Wolf looks like.
What we do know is
he's a former German nationaI
who sells atomic material
to terrorists all over the world.
Intelligence confirms that
a transaction is to take place
next week in Belgrade.
The Wolf's number one man,
the Albino,
will be selling a dirty bomb
to Syrian buyers.
MAN: We've already dispatched
a team to eliminate the buyers,
secure the bomb,
and apprehend the Albino.
How may I be of service, sir?
Your target is the Wolf.
We have reason to believe
he'll be present.
Find him and eliminate him.
Yes, sir.
Let them get the Albino,
you get the Wolf.
Oh, sir, if I may,
who is our agent on the ground?
MAN: Ethan Renner.
- He's a lifer.
- (COUGHING)
He'll get the job done.
MAN: The buyers have been neutralized.
Well done, Ethan. Well done.
(COMPUTERIZED VOICE)
Going down.
Maid service.
I have your extra towels.
ETHAN: This cold is killing me.
- (RASPY COUGH)
- (CELL PHONE RINGS)
- ETHAN: Yeah?
- WOMAN ON PHONE: Where are you?
- You left a big mess.
- Yeah, well...
...I'm thinking about calling in sick.
Come on, you haven't had
a sick day in 32 years.
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
- Here's the scanner.
- Thank you, Yasmin.
Uh... be sure to stock my bedroom with those
little shampoo bottles, I like them.
All teams in position.
(PHONE ALERT JINGLES)
Excuse me.
(COUGHING)
Nice work in there, my man.
- (PHONE ALERT JINGLES)
- Oh... it's Zooey's birthday.
I need a second to make a call.
Cell phones aren't secure, Ethan.
Yeah, well, it's my daughter.
You've got a payphone outside,
you've got five minutes.
Let's see the scan.
Hey, hey, listen I'm trying to
make a phone call over there and
I don't have any change so
if I could borrow some out of this money.
- [speaking foreign language]
- I can come back and I can pay you back.
Come on, come on.
Son of a bitch.
All right, this is worth a lot.
I take some of this.
I'm coming back for that.
Excuse me.
Have we met before?
You would remember me, no?
Karachi!
Yasmin's been compromised.
We need to move now, AxeI!
No one moves on the Albino
untiI we have cleared what's in the box.
Come on.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We met in Karachi last ApriI exactly.
But then you were working
as a cocktaiI waitress
if I remember it correctly?
(BEEPING)
- Oh, shit.
- We got confirmation.
MAN: That's a dirty bomb.
ALBINO: Boss.
MAN: Abort.
(LINE RINGING)
(GRUNTING SOFTLY)
(SPEAKS FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
- WOMAN ON PHONE: Hey.
- Hi sweetie, it's your father.
You didn't forget, which
means you probably love me.
Of course I do, Zooey.
You can prove it by singing me
"Happy Birthday," loudly.
Well, I could sweetheart,
but, uh, I'm at work.
You can leave a message
after the beep.
(MESSAGE BEEPS)
What the f...?
All right.
♪ Happy birthday to you
♪ Happy birth...
Go, go! Get in position!
Cover me!
- (TIRES SKID)
- ♪... to you
♪ Happy birthday, dear Zooey
(DISCONNECTED BEEPING)
(PATRONS SCREAMING)
AXEL: Cover Ethan now!
ETHAN: We're going in!
We're going in!
- (HIGH-PITCHED RINGING)
- AXEL: (MUFFLED) Cover Ethan! Cover Ethan!
(EMPTY GUN CLICKING)
(COUGHING)
All right, that's enough.
Put it down.
Now.
Now slide it over here.
You're not going to kill me, are you?
Not unless I have to, all right?
But I'm not running
after you anymore, fucker.
(SIRENS APPROACHING)
(ERRATIC HEARTBEATING)
Ohh...
(SHOUTS IN PAIN)
(INDISTINCT POLICE RADIO CHATTER)
(HELICOPTER HOVERING)
(CHILD GIGGLING)
I see you've read the report.
- It's called Glioblastoma.
- Yeah.
It's a type of brain cancer
and it's spread to your lungs.
It doesn't say
how much time I have left.
Three months, possibly five.
Yeah.
So, no Christmas this year, huh?
I'm afraid not.
I suggest you put your affairs in order.
MAN: Thank you, doctor.
Well done securing the bomb, Ethan.
But now that you're no longer operationaI,
we need to terminate our relationship.
We've wired your pension into your account.
The CIA thanks you
for your service.
(♪ANN PEEBLES: "TROUBLE,
HEARTACHES, AND SADNESS")
(KEYS JINGLING)
ETHAN: What the...?
(MAN SPEAKING MUFFLED FRENCH)
(UP-TEMPO SOUL MUSIC
PLAYING IN APARTMENT)
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
- What are you doing in my place?
- You do not speak French?
No, I'm American. I...
- I live here.
- Which floor?
No, I mean, I live here.
You? You are the owner?
I'm so happy to finally meet you.
ALL: Bonjour, mon ami.
This is my wife, Teresa.
My son Abbate.
My daughter Sumia is in the kitchen,
she's pregnant.
These are my cousins.
They are visiting us from Mali.
untiI they go to stay with
my brother in Saint-Denis.
- Do you know Saint Denis?
- No, I don't know Saint Denis.
- What are you doing in my apartment?
- We were without a home.
We were seeking shelter.
You are lucky we're here.
- Bad spirit fill empty spaces.
- Yeah, but now I'm back.
And it is good that you are finally back.
My name is Jules.
Ethan.
Where's all my stuff?
I also started to paint the room.
My wife think it is best to have
a cheerfuI color.
Is yellow good for you? I'm happy to do
the work. It's not a problem, Ethan.
Actually, Jules,
there is a problem.
(MAN SPEAKING FRENCH)
(HEAVY FRENCH ACCENT)
That's months from now.
Then I guess I need to throw
them out myself.
No, no, no, hey, ho.
(CLICKING TONGUE)
(ALL SHOUTING IN FRENCH)
I'll go to...
Hey! I'll go to jaiI?
[IN FRENCH]
All right, what exactly then
am I supposed to do?
Did you really just say that to me?
(ALL SHOUTING)
- (LIVELY SOUL MUSIC PLAYING)
- Ethan, Ethan!
I need to talk to your dad.
- (JULES SPEAKING FRENCH)
- Psst!
Please give me a minute
to finish my call.
- I'm sorry, Ethan.
- Let's talk in private, Jules, in my room.
I can assure you, we have not
touched any of your things.
I'm not saying you did,
but I think it's time you and I
got to know each other
just a little better.
'Cause you're notjust crashing
at some guy's house.
No problem, Ethan.
We will pack and leave now.
(JULES IN FRENCH)
Where are you gonna go
with a pregnant kid?
I don't know, but we'll
leave without packing.
Sit down.
You don't have to go yet,
Jules, at least...
...not untiI your daughter
has her baby.
But you stay under my rules.
- I am also a believer in rules.
- Rule #1, no one steps in this room again.
No one. Absolutely.
I'll put a bigger sign.
That's right,
you put a bigger sign.
Rule #2, you always do what
I say, no questions asked.
Yes, of course.
And rule #3, you don't
ever paint my room again.
- You don't like the color?
- No.
I told my wife yellow
is not a man's color.
No, yellow is not
a man's color.
- So you also have a daughter?
- Yes.
Like Sumia.
(GRUNTS)
OK, OK, no more yellow.
(SEAGULL CRIES)
(SIRENS BLARING)
(COUGHING)
(INDISTINCT VOICES ON TV)
WOMAN: Who is the most
beautiful girl in the world?
- Is that you?
- GIRL: Look, Daddy!
WOMAN: That is so cute!
(GIGGLING)
(PEACOCK TRILLING)
WOMAN: Run, run, run!
MAN: Hey, salut, Christine.
Hi, you.
(LINE RINGS)
- (CELL PHONE RINGTONE JINGLES)
- Hey.
[IN FRENCH]
- This is Christine.
- ETHAN: Hello, Tina. It's me.
I'm in town.
I'm in a meeting right now,
so this is not a good time to talk.
I don't want to talk.
I want to see you.
Yeah, I'm exceptionally busy,
so, uh... unless it's urgent
I've got some legaI stuff I need you
to look at before I leave town.
Why?
- Are you getting married?
- No, why, are you?
No, not today.
All right, I'll meet you outside.
OK, see ya.
(MUFFLED CHATTER)
Why are we really here, Ethan?
I wanted to see you.
And our daughter,
you want to see her too?
Yes. Yes.
I started a college fund.
Why the sudden interest?
It's not sudden, Tina.
I try to stay in touch.
I left her a message
on her birthday.
Yes, and now she'll have to wait
another year to hear from you again.
I'm dying, Tina.
- You think this is easy for me?
- No, I'm...
(COUGHS) I'm sick.
I mean, I'm dying.
MAN: Sorry it took so long,
but I'm afraid your will
must be signed
in both French and English.
ETHAN: I don't want Zooey to know,
at least not right away.
Come on in.
It's nice.
The place looks better than before.
Don't look too hard.
It's falling apart.
I know I haven't done right
by you and Zooey.
I want to see her before I go.
You have to make me a promise.
I'll let you see her under one condition.
Are you done?
Are you really done working for them?
- Yes.
- Promise me.
Yes. I missed a lot.
I should have left a long time ago.
- (SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
- I'm gonna be fine.
I've got the whole day planned.
First...
Oh, no, no, sweetheart, no.
She has her own plans.
You'll just have to catch up.
Hi, sweetie!
Hi.
Hi, Zooey.
How are you?
I'm good, how are you?
I'm good, thank you.
- TINA: OK.
- Mom, please don't cry. I'm fine.
No, I'm just... I'll be
back home at 8:30. Yeah?
What are we supposed to do?
All right, how about I cook?
You're on.
So you want me to call you Dad
or should I just call you Ethan?
I think I like Dad.
Favorite place to go after schooI?
I didn't know
we had a favorite place.
Flying chairs, remember?
Look, Ethan, we don't need
to do this, all right?
I know you probably want to talk
and get to know each other.
That's why I transferred
back here to Paris.
Look, I'm not mad at you,
all right?
I don't need you to explain any of this,
all right? It's not a big deaI.
Come on, Zoe,
let's go to the cafe.
Hugh, I want you to meet Ethan.
Who?
- I'm Zooey's father.
- Oh! Hello.
No.
Well, great to meet you,
Ethan... Mr. Renner.
Sorry, sometimes
I just get a bit nervous
when I see American cowboys.
(MAKES SHOOTING SOUNDS)
Yee-haw!
OK.
He's older than you.
Yeah, he's a senior.
Is there something wrong with that?
Back when I was growing up if you...
Hugh is so different than you.
Look, I know I'm blowing it here,
Zooey, I...
- Look, I...
- (RINGS BIKE BELL)
...thought you might
want to ride this home.
- Wow, is this for me?
- Yeah.
It's... so purple.
Yeah, it's your favorite color.
Right, when I was like nine.
I'm taking the metro with my friends.
All right, so I'll see you
at home for dinner?
(♪ TALISCO: "YOUR WISH")
Zooey, I'll see you at home for dinner?
(BELL TOLLING)
- How are these?
- Fresh.
They're fresh?
I just need to steam them, right?
WOMAN: Don't forget to soak it in milk.
Milk?
Only if you plan to fry it.
(CHUCKLES) Haven't got that far.
I like a man that doesn't pretend to know
his way around the kitchen.
Yeah, well, you're talking
to the right guy.
Yes...
...I think I am.
Well, I'm soaking tuna in milk and
thanks to you,
frying it for my daughter.
So today is Zooey's lucky day?
What did you say your name was?
You can call me Vivi.
Nice running into you, Vivi,
but not interested.
Maybe we could talk?
My wife gave me this.
Come on, cheri,
let's go for a drive.
All right,
but my bike's coming with me.
The bike's going with me.
Who exactly do you work for, Vivi?
I work for the director of the CIA.
Wouldn't know about the top shelf.
Serbia was my operation.
I was looking for the Wolf.
We believe he was
at the hoteI that day,
and I believe that
you may have seen him.
- Wait a minute.
- And I'm willing to bet
that when you see him again
you'll recognize him.
I want you to come work for me.
Not a chance.
I've already got plans.
Don't you think Zooey deserves
to have her daddy around
for more than just
a few measly months?
(TIRES SKID)
Jesus!
That was really close.
In exchange for your cleaning services,
I could offer you an experimentaI drug.
Interested?
This, Ethan,
could extend your life.
Where's the literature?
You know, the test results.
How come no one's told me
about this before?
Because you weren't worth
the cost of treatment.
Wow. You make me feeI so speciaI.
- You weren't. But now you are.
- Why?
Because you're sick and dead men
have nothing to lose.
I have access to many things, Ethan,
but only you can give me
access to the Wolf.
I need you to find him...
...and I need you to kill him.
So I buy back my life by killing for you?
When did you become so self-righteous?
Jesus Christ, I just wanna be sure
that we're talking about the same thing here.
You know, killing.
There's a man inside that works
for the Wolf's accountant.
I'm gonna need you
to start right away.
Well, I got a fish to fry and I'm late.
I can get you in home
in time for dinner, Ethan.
Question is...
...do you want your bike back?
- Pretty public place.
- Meaning?
Meaning a silencer would...
...be handy.
So, how many guys
are we talking about?
One.
Knock 'em dead.
Yeah, well, that's the point, isn't it?
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- (TELEPHONE RINGS)
- (SPEAKING FRENCH)
- Allo?
- (MAN OVER PHONE)
(MAN SHOUTS)
(GASPING)
Grenade!
(SILENCED GUNSHOT)
VIVI: Pretty good for a jobber.
You said there'd be one guy,
not five.
VIVI: Oops.
But I did say keep the young man
with the mustache alive.
What do you think
this guy looks like?
(PANTING)
- Middle-aged.
- Not a chance.
- Tell her how old you are.
- I am...
Make an effort, all right?
I'm trying to save your life.
- Now tell her how old you are.
- I'm 32.
- Middle-aged.
- Jesus Christ!
Now this...
(GROANS)
...is a young man with a mustache.
No, that's a goatee.
That's a mustache and some stubble.
- That's a goatee.
- That's a goatee?
That's a mustache, all right?
This is a goatee.
- That's a shadow.
- It looks French.
- Since when?
- That's a goatee...
What, from your century, grandpa?
Look at that, that's a mustache.
All right, so what about
the rest of these guys?
- Hmm?
- Oh, my...
Who are all these other guys here?
- I don't know.
- And that doesn't bother you?
Nope.
Because I usually like to know the person
I'm killing needs to be dead.
And that's why you never made it
to the top shelf, my friend.
Goatee, you're up.
I'm looking for the accountant.
When does he get back to Paris?
I don't know, I swear.
Kill him.
Hold on,
I can get this guy to talk.
(GROANS)
He didn't know.
ETHAN: Goddamn it.
Do you even have a line
that can't be crossed?
(DOOR OPENS)
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
I'm gonna need a significant raise.
I wanna leave my daughter
more than just my shit pension.
Look, I'll close at 25 but I'm gonna cap you
to half a dozen kills.
Half a dozen?
I'm already halfway there.
We've all been asked
to tighten our belts.
Don't take this the wrong way,
Viv, but you're not my type.
(SCOFFS)
I'm everybody's type.
- You... Are you sure this works?
- No.
But I am sure that if you don't try it,
you'll be dead in two months.
It's 50 thousand, not 25.
And you're giving me credit
for those three guys upstairs.
And I'm also gonna want a...
I'm gonna need a million
dollar life insurance policy.
Take it or leave it.
I'll take it.
I like the package.
All right, now do it.
Breathe, Ethan.
It will hit you morphine-quick.
One way or another...
...I will make you feeI better.
Don't forget to soak the fish.
You promised me my bike.
(BIKE BELL RINGS)
(ZOOEY SCREAMS)
Zooey!
- Zooey! Are you OK?
- No, I'm not OK.
(♪ MAKE THE GIRL DANCE: "KILL ME")
Look at this.
This looks terrible.
I think your...
Your hair?
No, no.
Yes. Yes, my hair.
I look like a freaking Chia Pet.
It looks, uh, awesome.
- Really?
- Yeah.
You think this can go to prom?
Well, if you're going you might
as well take it with you.
- Oh, is that some kind ofjoke?
- No, no, I mean...
All these times,
now's the time to say a joke?
No, I mean, maybe...
- Maybe we can fix your hair.
- Fix it? You can fix this?
No, you can...
You could wash it...
You could sleep on it and,
look, tomorrow it will be...
It'll be back to normaI,
all right? Maybe?
- You really think so?
- Yeah.
ETHAN: Why don't we
pick up some dinner?
(SHOUTS)
Hey. Don't offer to cook dinner
if you're going to be three hours late.
Look, I'm sorry, Tina, but I was...
Save it. I was crazy
to think I could count on you.
I was gonna ask you to look after Zooey
while I go to London for work.
- Then, go.
- (SCOFFS)
Really, you should go,
I can handle it.
You can't handle dinner.
How are you gonna handle a teenager?
How about I just diffused
a major meltdown. Her hair, OK?
I have to take the first flight
out tomorrow morning.
I'm calling a sitter.
I was late because I found
a doctor who can help me.
- What?
- There's, um...
There's a specialist here
in Paris who has
a experimentaI drug
she's willing to test on me.
ExperimentaI.
What exactly does that mean?
It means I might be able to spend a little
more time with you and Zooey.
You should have called, Ethan,
because I was going to kill you.
Can we just, like, maybe quit
fighting for a second.
Maybe not talk about
killing someone? Me.
I could grill us up some of this tuna.
- Tuna?
- Yeah.
- Tuna.
- With all that mercury?
No way!
(DOO-WOP MUSIC PLAYING)
You're gonna fix that door, right?
Oh. Um...
Yeah, that was a mistake.
You haven't been here 24 hours.
I hope the sofa is going
to be comfortable.
Yeah. Better than a cot in Karachi.
Do you need something
to help you sleep?
Yeah, I'm gonna need it now.
(CHUCKLES)
You're terrible.
(ERRATIC HEARTBEAT)
(GRUNTING)
(CELL PHONE BUZZING)
VIVI: I knew you would call.
What the hell did you give me?
- You're not coming over?
- No. I'm dizzy.
My head... My head's dizzy.
(WHISPERS) Vivi.
- (CELL PHONE BUZZES)
- (SIGHS)
- Read the manuaI.
- Wait! I'm hallucinating.
I'm hallucinating.
- Take a shot of vodka.
- What?
Vodka. It'll take the edge off.
(GROANS)
Is everything OK?
Yeah.
- I had a little trouble finding the vodka.
- Huh.
(BELLS TOLLING)
Listen, you can call me
anytime you want.
It's only a one hour difference
between Paris and London.
- There you are.
- And you can call me, too.
- I love you.
- ZOOEY: All right.
I'll be back in a couple of days,
I'm running late.
- Your daddy has a list.
- Kind of a big list.
- Washing powder...
- I'll see you guys!
- Have fun!
- ... for black clothes. (GROANS)
Zooey, come on, breakfast.
Look at me. Come on.
Just one time up here.
One time.
(CHUCKLES)
Atta girl.
Zooey!
(SPITS)
Oh.
What?
Wow, it's...
- It's what?
- Geez.
- So, what, Ethan?
- It's...
- It's so red.
- (CELL PHONE VIBRATES)
ZOOEY: Vivi?
Are you going to get that?
Sorry. Nobody important,
just my boss, Vivi.
Was she the one calling you
in the middle of the night?
We talk a lot because
we sell internationally.
It's always daytime somewhere.
All right, so now we've got
three days to kill.
What are you doing?
It's called a ringtone, Ethan.
I'm giving you mine.
Maybe we can talk more
than once a year.
(PHONE PLAYS ICONA POP:
"I LOVE IT")
There. Welcome to this century.
- (BIKE BELL RINGS)
- Zooey. Zooey.
Don't you want to ride
your bike to schooI?
You think Hugh's
gonna like my hair color?
Yes, I do.
- Really?
- Yes.
- You think he'll really love it?
- Well, if he cares about you he will.
So you don't love it?
No.
No, I mean, yes, Zooey.
Zooey, I really love it.
- Awesome.
- (COUGHS)
(COUGHING)
I can see you don't
believe in the customary
forty-eight-hour window between kills.
Well, you only have three days left.
I'm not getting into your car, Vivi.
Not untiI I get a second opinion on that
whatever it was you gave me.
- I told you it's kosher.
- No, it's not.
- Aw.
- The manuaI says,
if you'd bothered to read it,
you'd find out if I can't keep
my heart rate lower,
that shit's gonna act
like a hallucinogen.
So keep your heart rate low.
Yeah, well, it's kind of hard
with the job you got me doing.
Get in the car already.
I need you to locate
the Italian accountant
who cooks the books
for your old friend the Albino.
How am I supposed to locate this guy?
With the help of this man.
His name is Mitat Yilmaz.
He runs a limo service
that caters to the Albino.
Get to know him, he'll lead you
straight to the accountant.
All right.
- And, Ethan?
- Yeah?
Lose the bike.
- Buy a suit.
- Why?
(SCOFFS)
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
(MAN LAUGHING)
So, you understand we are
a luxury car service, right?
- Yeah.
- How did you come to hear of us?
An Albino told me.
Did he also tell you
that we offer discreet luxury?
He told me not to talk to the hired help,
to talk to the boss.
We're not the help, OK?
We are the executive vice president of sales.
- Ooohh!
- (BOTH LAUGHING)
You're a couple of turds.
[IN FRENCH]
Listen, asshole...
...little piece of turd,
you're nobody to us.
And you will never meet the boss.
Understand?
All right, I'm sorry.
Yeah.
I had a really weird night,
you know,
a couple ofweird nights.
Jetlagged.
I think maybe we got
off on the wrong foot. My fault.
Yeah.
- Can we start again?
- (SCOFFS)
Let's start again.
Jesus Christ, I'm starting to think
you can see the EiffeI Tower from
everywhere in this town.
(SILENCED GUNSHOT)
(UP-TEMPO FOREIGN POP SONG PLAYS)
(SINGS ALONG WITH SONG)
(CONTINUES SINGING POP SONG)
You are a very rude man
to sit behind my desk
without an invitation, Mr...?
Why are names important right now?
Because I don't want
to kill a totaI stranger.
What do you want
to kill me for, Mitat?
You are sitting in my chair.
I'm just waiting for you.
(MEN GROANING)
The Albino sent you, huh?
Bastard!
I've always been loyaI.
Please...
- These your girls in the picture?
- How dare you look at them?!
Sit down.
I also have a pretty teenage daughter.
Father to father,
your girls ever
lock themselves in their room,
you know?
Cut their hair, paint it red, you know?
Put wigs on and shit like that?
No. Never.
I knew it! I'm in trouble.
(MEN GROANING)
- So the Albino didn't send you to kill me?
- No.
(GRUNTING)
Then who are you?
Ethan. Come on.
( GROOVE CENTURY: "SOUL SEARCHING" PLAYS)
♪ Soul searching
♪ Ain't no finer groove
♪ Gonna make you move
♪ Well
I'm gonna have a conversation
with this man in the bathroom.
I do not want to be disturbed.
Yes. Rule #2:
Do whatever you say.
That's right, Rule #2.
- He's a bad guy?
- Something like that.
And you are a good guy?
You are a professionaI, huh?
Why have I never seen you
in Paris before?
I've been away on business
for about five years.
What is so important that you'd
leave your daughter so long?
Well, I was never good
at balancing work and family.
(GROANING)
You know, when I go home,
this life, the killing,
the rest it all disappears.
I made the wrong choice leaving.
Everyday I bring my girls to schooI
and I have dinner with my family.
That's the key.
Oh, good for you, Mitat.
So let's not miss dinner tonight, hmm?
When is the accountant
arriving in Paris?
Please remind me,
who is he again?
(SQUEALS)
- (GROANS)
- (CELL PHONE RINGING)
- Hello?
- Hello, Mrs. DriskaI here.
I'd like to have a word with
Zooey's father.
I'm Zooey's father.
Is she all right?
Zooey's fine,
but we need to meet.
We need to have a conversation
about Zooey's behavior.
(MUFFLED WHIMPERING)
I can be there right away.
Well, do hurry.
We're going to schooI.
As I was saying to Zooey,
study after study has shown that
aggression is exacerbated
by violent images in popular culture.
Well, Zooey's mother
raised her to be a pacifist.
Hm.
Hitting a classmate in the face
is hardly a passive response.
With an open hand
or a clenched fist?
- What difference does that make?
- Well, from my experience,
anger, frustration, insult,
they all call for...
...they all call for different responses.
Mr. Renner, it's extremely important
that you send your daughter
a clear message
that no matter what she
has to confront in life
violence is not
an acceptable answer.
I'll try.
If that wasn't so weird, it would have
been really embarrassing, Ethan.
- Let me see your hand.
- What?
Let me see your hand, Zooey.
Ow, my thumb.
If you're gonna hit someone
with a clenched fist
be sure to not tuck your thumb in.
You've been gone for five years
and this is what you say to me?
- Oh, God.
- (BIKE BELL DINGS)
(MITAT THUMPING IN TRUNK)
(FOREIGN POP SONG PLAYS)
- Are you Muslim?
- No.
I told you this is my boss's car.
- Oh, so Vivi's Muslim?
- No.
- I'm plugging in my phone. This stuff sucks.
- I know.
(♪ MAKE THE GIRL DANCE: "KILL ME")
I like this,
who are these guys?
- Do you even care why I got into a fight?
- MITAT: Let me out!
(TURNS VOLUME UP)
Why can't you just listen to me
and try to understand?
OK, why don't you tell me all about it?
I have a new friend from Pakistan,
and there's this British girI
who keeps calling her Paki.
Today she put bacon in her locker,
so I hit her in the face.
Well, she won't do that again, will she?
(THUMPING CONTINUES)
Just a second, sweetie,
sounds like the spare's loose in the trunk.
Hey!
I'm trying to have a conversation
with my daughter.
I'm... I'm sorry, sweetie,
now where were we?
- Punching the girI, right?
- I feeI really bad.
Well, don't, because sometimes
it's the only way to stop a bad guy.
- So you're not mad at me?
- No, I'm not mad at you.
I'm proud of you,
you stuck up for your friend.
Whatever. I'm taking the metro.
- And, Ethan?
- Yeah.
You might want to take something
for that cough. It's really annoying.
Jesus Christ!
Let's see ifwe can
jump start your memory, Mitat.
(ZOOEY'S RINGTONE PLAYS)
- It's my daughter.
- (GROANS)
- Zooey?
- Hey. Sorry about earlier.
That's OK, honey.
I'm sorry, too.
Favorite place to hang out after schooI?
(ELECTRICAL ZAPPING)
I'll wrap my sales meeting
and meet you at 3:30, sweetie.
She just invited me to hang out.
What do you think about that?
A girl like this will keep you
running in circles.
You must draw the line,
not be so soft.
You're right, Mitat.
I have been way too soft.
- (CURRENT ZAPPING)
- (SHOUTING IN PAIN)
Now, where do I find
the Albino's accountant, hmm?
(YELLING)
(ZOOEY'S RINGTONE PLAYS)
Hi, Zooey.
It's 3:40, Ethan.
Where are you?
I'm on my bike, sweetie.
Forget it, you're always late.
I'm leaving.
No, no, no, I'm almost there,
honestly, Zooey.
Give me...
Give me five minutes.
Fine, five minutes.
I have homework.
Wow.
Kids.
(♪ASAF AVIDAN:
"LOVE IT OR LEAVE IT")
ZOOEY: Sorry I freaked out earlier.
It's just Hugh and the prom
and you came into town.
ETHAN: This is really new for both of us.
I get it.
So, favorite place to go after Flying Chairs,
you remember?
- I remember.
- Kind of?
- Yeah.
- OK.
- (BELL RINGING)
- Gosh, the bike.
(ETHAN COUGHING HARSHLY)
What's going on, Ethan?
It's just some flu I picked up.
Can't seem to shake it off.
What if it's something worse?
No, it's, uh...
It's nothing worse.
You remember when we'd drink
hot chocolate at the beach house?
Sort of.
It's the one place I wouldn't
mind calling home.
- More than Pittsburgh, really?
- Yeah, more than Pittsburgh.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
You know, I kept all
our home movies in a box.
How about we make dinner
and watch them tonight?
- Yeah, that'd be awesome.
- Good.
Oh, shoot, I forgot.
I have to go to Karina's tonight.
- Who?
- Karina, she's my lab partner.
We're doing a science project together.
I'm going to spend the night.
- On a schooI night?
- Yeah. I'm sorry, Ethan, I'm really sorry.
No, it's OK. It's just...
Don't I need to call her parents first?
Yeah, if you speak Russian.
That's all her parents understand.
Look, call Mom.
She'll tell you it's cooI.
I don't need to call your mom.
- Can we watch those movies tomorrow?
- Yeah, sure.
See you later.
(LINE RINGS, VOICEMAIL ANSWERS)
Hi, this is Christine, I'm not here,
so please leave a message.
Tina, it's me.
Can you believe Zooey and I
hung out on flying chairs
and we had hot chocolate
and it was her idea?
Thanks for all this, Tina.
You're a really great mom.
(LOW-TEMPO POP SONG PLAYS)
(CUSTOMERS SCREAMING)
(STARTLED CRY)
(MAN SCREAMS)
(BOTH MEN GRUNTING)
- (FLESH SIZZLING)
- (SCREAMING)
(BOTH MEN SHOUTING)
- (MULTIPLE GUNSHOTS)
- (GRUNTING)
(WOMAN YELLS)
(CELL PHONE BUZZING)
TINA: Hi, I'm thrilled
everything's going so well.
But, uh, who is this friend?
Well, I've never heard of her
nor her Russian parents.
Anyways, give me a call.
Zooey!
(MUFFLED TECHNO MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC VOLUME GETS LOUDER)
Non, non.
Son of a bitch!
Is this your car?
Pardon... Is this your car?
- Whoa.
- No.
(ALL SHOUTING)
Hey! You know the rule.
Never involve family.
This isn't a business meeting,
Mitat, this is...
(BOTH STRAINING)
This is more of a
father-to-father type of visit.
- It's dinner time.
- WOMAN: Mitat?
- Do you know this man, Mitat?
- Yeah, we work together.
- Never seen him before.
- It's an American.
OK. Come, come with us.
Thanks for that.
This is Rachelle, Sarah.
I have a serious problem
with my daughter, Zooey.
You've been gone for five years
and you did not expect trouble?
- We cannot help you.
- That's right, you probably can't.
But your girls might
be able to tell me where
a 16-year-old would go
to party on a schooI night.
What does this "spider" mean?
WOMAN: They are good girls,
they do not party.
What does this "spider" mean?
BOTH: La Soiree House.
- How do you know that?
- Thank you.
(CROWD CHATTERING)
- (SPEAKING FRENCH)
- I have a daughter in there.
(SILENCED GUNSHOT)
(LOUD TECHNO MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC BECOMES MUFFLED)
- (MAN SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
- Zooey.
ZOOEY: Oui.
(SOUNDS BECOME DISTORTED)
Zooey!
(PANTING)
Stop, please, please.
(RAP SONG PLAYS)
(SPEAKS FRENCH)
Stop, please.
(MEN SPEAKING FRENCH)
Ethan!
- (BONES CRACKING)
- (PAINFUL SHOUTING)
Ethan! Please!
Come on, Zooey. Come on.
I got you, honey.
(BELL TOLLING)
What are you doing here?
Better question, Zooey, is,
what were you doing last night?
God, this is so embarrassing.
They'll never let me in there again.
Why would you ever want to go
back to a place like that?
Because I like
being with my friends.
Your friends?
Do you even remember
what happened?
In the bathroom?
- Zooey!
- What?
In the bathroom,
do you remember what happened?
Look, Karina and I
aced the practice test, OK?
- No, you didn't.
- Yes, we did.
So we decided to go hang out
with some friends.
I've gotta go catch the metro,
I'm gonna be late for schooI.
- You're not going to the metro.
- What?
You're not going to schooI today.
Not dressed like that.
You're putting this on and we're going home.
- We're gonna have a talk.
- How exactly am I supposed to get home?
- Gonna ride this bike.
- I don't think so, Ethan.
You're getting on this bike and I'm gonna
follow you every step of the way.
- No, you're not.
- Stop talking and get on the bike.
I thought that's what you
wanted to do, Ethan, talk!
Get on this bike.
- Or what?
- Now!
I don't even know how
to ride a bike, OK?
What kind of kid doesn't know
how to ride a bike?
The kind of kid who never
had a father to teach her.
Goddamn it.
This is the flattest spot,
so let's just try it right here.
Gosh, did you have to get
the biggest bike there?
It's not the biggest bike,
Zooey, it's a girI's bike.
Right, you picked it
'cause it had the big bow on it.
No. I can explain the big bow,
I got it. Get on.
There's too many people.
Look, can we go somewhere private?
- Gosh.
- There's not too many people.
But it's purple.
It is purple. Get on.
- How do you even get on it?
- Just get on.
Wow, we did it.
We're halfway there. We're on it.
(SHUSHES)
Give yourself time to push here, OK?
It's right here then. All right?
Zooey, all right.
- Whoa. OK?
- OK.
- Good.
- Easy, please.
OK, I have you. Now, just
kinda, you know how to pedaI.
- Yes. I'm right here.
- Why is it so high?
Don't let go. I'm gonna...
ZOOEY: Why did you leave us, Ethan?
Why did you leave me and Mom?
ETHAN: Look, I traveled a lot, sweetheart,
and your mother and I...
- (GRUNTING)
- ZOOEY: What?
There is no easy...
There's no good answer, honey.
All right.
- Do you have another family?
- No. No, sweetheart. I didn't. Come on.
ZOOEY: Do you have another family?
- Is that what it is?
- ETHAN: No.
ZOOEY: Do you have another
perfect daughter somewhere?
Did you see me and not want me?
- Do you not love me?
- No, sweetheart, no, that's not it.
ZOOEY: Well, why did it take so long
for you to come back?
Look! (LAUGHS)
ETHAN: The longer I was gone...
...it felt like the harder
it was to come back.
(APPLAUSE)
OK, OK, all right.
That's all.
It's nothing to do with you.
ZOOEY: Would you still care about me
if I did horrible things?
Yes, of course.
Absolutely.
I lie a lot.
Like, all the time about everything.
Even when I don't need to.
I don't know why.
Well, you know, sometimes that's
easier than telling the truth.
That girI I hit at schooI,
she wasn't teasing a Pakistani friend.
She was hitting on Hugh.
- It's all right, he prefers soccer.
- Yeah.
ZOOEY: Hugh!
These are so beautifuI, thank you!
Give me one sec, I'll be right back.
Ethan, don't say anything weird.
- You rave, Hugh?
- What?
- You rave?
- No, no way, Mr. Zoe.
I'm an athlete.
I'm a striker.
Last game I scored two goals,
by the way.
- So you like to score?
- Yeah, yeah, definitely, yeah.
No! Well, I...
I... I mean on the field.
- Yeah.
- On the field only, yeah.
- Soccer?
- Yeah.
Not a fan. I'm from Pittsburgh,
where we play real football.
- Oh yeah, American football.
- No.
ReaI football.
OK.
Nice bike.
- You like the bike?
- Yeah.
You're the only one.
I won't be home late, Ethan.
- Where are you two going?
- SchooI.
Great, well,
I'm headed that direction myself.
No, you're not.
Yeah, well, I could be.
I'm going to the market.
Oh, OK, well, I'm gonna...
OK, see you later,
Mr. Zooey.
I don't like being called that.
You don't like Hugh?
(LAUGHS) I'm in, uh, sales, sweetie.
It's my business to read people.
You know, a lot of my friends'
dads are in sales, Ethan,
and not one of them
dresses like you.
What are you saying?
I'm saying they wear suits.
That's what they wear to work.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
Hey, I love you!
(CHUCKLES)
- (GROANS) Haven't I helped you enough?
- You know the drill.
The accountant checked out.
I need you to tell me where he is now.
- I gave him to you yesterday.
- I know you did.
And now you're back.
I thought you were a pro.
I'm suddenly a single dad.
It's getting complicated.
Is it my fault if your daughter
is out of controI
and affecting your work and judgment?
You're right, Mitat.
It is affecting my judgment.
'Cause you should have
been dead a long time ago.
Hey, my wife works late.
I need to pick up my girls at 4:30.
I can't promise,
but I'll make an effort.
(DEVICE BEEPING)
Open up.
I can't get around your mirror.
(MUTTERING IN ITALIAN)
Fine, asshole.
(SHOUTING)
(BOTH SPEAKING FRENCH)
(COUGHING)
Yes!
Ethan! Ethan!
(DUCT TAPE RIPPING)
That briefcase has the routing codes
to the Albino's accounts, doesn't it?
Yeah.
Do not open!
The lock has an explosive trigger.
I got the codes to the briefcase.
Give me the codes to the trigger, Guido.
But after I give it to you,
you will kill me.
No, but I swear to God
I'm gonna really torture you
- if you make me count to three.
- No.
- OK, one...
- Oh, no.
- ... two
- No.
- (ZOOEY'S RINGTONE PLAYS)
- Zooey?
- Ethan, so listen,
I was thinking about tonight.
Sweetie, I'm gonna be home on time for
dinner, all right? I promise. Now, can I...
- Can I call you back?
- I want to make dinner for Hugh tonight.
Just the two of you, like a...
- ... romantic dinner?
- Something like that.
And I want to make him
reaI spaghetti sauce
but I don't know what I need
besides tomatoes.
I can't find Mom,
so I need your help.
Just a sec, sweetie.
Guido, are you a reaI Italian?
What?
I mean, are you a reaI Italian?
I mean, were you born there?
Yes. Catania, Sicily.
Could she have a recipe for sauce?
Sauce?
Yeah, sauce, you know, sauce.
- Is that code?
- No, it's not code.
- You just said you're a reaI Italian, right?
- Si.
Si, so you must know a little
something about spaghetti sauce!
Ah! Spaghetti sauce!
Red or white?
- Red or white?
- Red, vegetable, not too spicy.
Vegetarian, not too spicy.
OK, I know what to tell her.
Sweetie, itjust so happens I'm in a meeting
here with a reaI live Italian.
His mama has a great recipe.
He wants to give it to you.
His name is Guido.
Why don't you say hello
to my daughter.
Hello. I am Guido.
Hi, Guido,
this will only take a second.
No, no!
- Please take all the time you want.
- (MUMBLES) Who's Guido?
No, no, no.
So, this is my mama's favorite
reduction sauce.
You will need tomatoes,
capers and garlic.
She always uses tomatoes
from her garden.
Your mom has a garden?
That is so cooI.
Yes, she worked all her life
so I could go to schooI,
and now I am the only one left
to take care of her.
- (SMACKS HIM WITH THE GUN)
- (MUTTERING)
What else, Guido?
Heat the olive oiI,
crush the garlic.
Then you peeI the tomatoes.
After ten minutes, no more,
add capers and parsley.
And my mama's secret
is a cup of red wine
and a teaspoon of sugar.
Boy, that Guido's a reaI mama's boy, huh?
I think it's sweet that he
loves his mother. Thanks, Ethan.
- Remember, don't get home too early.
- OK.
No, wait!
Oh, please call her back.
I wanted to give her my mama's
favorite recipe for cannoli.
You know how to tell time?
Where's the one?
Where's the three?
That's two hours.
You cut this guy loose
in two hours.
Guido, remind me where you're going
after this kid lets you go.
GUIDO: I'm going back home
to live with Mama!
(SULTRY FOREIGN POP SONG PLAYS)
You're late.
I'm in the middle
of a training session.
Yeah, I... I can see that.
Job's done.
- You're no fun.
- Not really.
Sit down.
Or did you forget why you came?
- Champagne?
- I don't think so.
You're just an American girI having
a good time in Paris, aren't you?
Who doesn't love Paris?
Now that we've bankrupted the Albino,
he'll come running back to Paris
with his tail between his legs,
leading us straight to the Wolf.
When?
Very soon.
You can't go dressed like that.
What's wrong with how I dress?
What are you, cheri, 42 long?
Yes.
- Take it off.
- Excuse me?
Shoes, everything. Let's go.
- What's going on?
- Baby.
Baby?
You let that guy go, right?
You didn't hurt him?
No, you keep that,
that's yours now.
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- (SUMIA BREATHING DEEPLY)
(ALL SPEAKING FRENCH)
My God.
This is not the first time
for you, after all.
Actually, it is.
What about your daughter?
I wasn't there.
I was working far away,
in Africa to be precise.
You were doing good?
I don't even remember.
- TERESA: The baby is coming!
- (BABY CRYING)
(SOFT APPLAUSE, CHEERING)
It is a girI.
(EXCITED CHATTER)
Before the baby leaves the house
for the first time,
it is our custom to have
the family offer a blessing.
- Leave?
- Yes.
- We are keeping our word to you.
- Word?
What word? I mean,
I just I brought Chinese, OK?
I've got a 100 fortune cookies.
It's OK.
Everything is as it should be.
Look, I didn't mean for you to have
to leave right after the child was born.
I mean, there's plenty of room
for everyone.
Maybe it's too much room.
My wife wants a smaller place
out of the city. No guests.
Just us and the children.
It is good
as long as we are together.
Sumia wants to call the baby Ethan.
- It's a boy's name.
- No.
It's the name of a great man
who didn't shoot us when he could.
And instead gave us his home.
She has chosen carefully.
The name is perfect.
Hey, how did it go?
Hugh asked me to go to the prom.
Good.
So dinner was a success.
Wow. You look nice.
Did you wear that for me today?
Uh... no. I had to...
I had to give a speech.
Are you coming to the pre-party tomorrow?
Well, I am if you're asking.
It's on Hugh's father's rooftop.
You know Hugh comes from
a really cultured family.
Yeah.
Don't forget you've got Steelers blood
running through your veins.
They sent Hugh to a speciaI schooI to learn
how to dance when he was like eight.
So?
So that means he's probably
a really good dancer.
So?
So I don't know how to dance
like that, Ethan.
(♪ BREAD: "MAKE IT WITH YOU")
- No.
- Come on.
- I'm not gonna dance.
- You can stand on my feet.
- I'm too big for this.
- You're not too big.
Now, stand on my feet.
I'm gonna teach you how to dance
to your mother's favorite song.
OK.
There and back.
- Pretty easy, huh?
- Not too bad.
- Now get off.
- (BOTH LAUGH)
Would you wear this suit
tomorrow for me?
Of course I would.
Mom.
Sweetie.
TINA: You haven't coughed.
Not since I've been back.
How are you feeling?
ETHAN: Remember when I'd bring Zooey
to school in the first grade?
She had that stuffed rabbit.
Lamby the lamb.
(CHUCKLES) Right, Lamby the lamb.
I remember the day
she never took him to school again.
My stomach hurt that day.
That's how I feel now.
- TINA: Like you lost something.
- Yeah.
- Have you told her yet?
- No.
- You're gonna have to.
- I know.
Just tell her you love her.
She knows.
She needs to hear it from you.
Of course I love her.
I mean, I love her the same way...
...the same way I love you.
Good morning.
Oh, God.
- You're not on the couch.
- No, Tina, I'm not on the couch.
Good morning, parents.
Wow, sweetheart.
What a good idea. Here.
Bring that orange juice right here.
Sweetie, just put down the tray,
I'll meet you in the kitchen. OK?
Come on,
I squeezed the oranges all by myself.
Now, please.
What's wrong, Mom?
You're acting really weird.
Nothing, sweetie. Just go finish getting
dressed and I'll take you to schooI.
Come on, let' go. Go.
Love you, Mom.
I love you, sweetie.
What's wrong with her seeing us?
Really.
What happens when you're gone?
(CELL PHONE VIBRATES)
Yeah?
VIVI: The Albino is staying
at the Grand Hotel.
All right.
Hey. I'm not going anywhere.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
- Hello.
- ETHAN: You spotted me.
- I'd have to be blind not to.
- Don't do anything stupid, Mitat.
Your girls are expecting you
home tonight.
So is your beautiful wife.
Who were you talking to?
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(CAR HONKS HORN)
Come on, accelerate!
Come on!
Come on, faster!
(GUN CLICKING)
Have we lost him?
This kind of guy,
he'd never give up.
(SCREAMING)
(MITAT SCREAMS)
Why you don't kill me already?
Because you're the father who knows best.
(HEARTBEATS)
(WOLF SHOUTING)
(ERRATIC HEARTBEAT)
(SOUNDS BECOME DISTORTED)
(SHOUTS IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
(RESPONDS IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
(WOLF SPEAKING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
(SPEAKING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
Just kill him!
(PASSENGERS SCREAMING)
(LOUD HEARTBEATS)
Vivi...
(CHILD GIGGLES)
(WHALE CALLING)
Welcome back.
You let the Wolf
slip through your hands again.
Where am I?
A safe place.
We got your lab results
back today, Ethan.
I was actually pretty curious myself.
And as it turns out,
it looks like the treatment's
having a positive effect on you.
It's my wife. Hello?
Hi. Where are you?
Um...
I'm leaving the doctor's office now.
Hurry up and get home.
We're gonna be late for Zooey's party.
OK.
I don't want to spend the rest of my life
killing for you, Vivi.
You're almost there, Ethan.
Kill the Wolf.
I'm gonna need a new suit.
(SIGHS)
You heard him.
There has been a change in plans.
We're leaving tonight.
Take me to my partner's house.
He will help me to get out of Paris.
- Mom, don't ruin my night.
- Why don't you try them on?
No!
- TINA: Listen, just at least try them on?
- ZOOEY: No!
(SIGHS)
Whoa!
Just smile and have fun.
Why? I hate these shoes.
I look like Little Miss Sunshine.
(MUZAK PLAYS SOFTLY)
- You look great, honey.
- No, I don't.
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
- Zoe.
- Hugh.
- You look great.
- Really, I do?
Yeah, of course.
Oh, Mr. Renner, Mrs. Renner,
these are my parents.
Nice to see you again.
Thanks for inviting us.
You're welcome.
This is Ethan, Zooey's dad.
Hi. And this is my partner.
Pleasure to meet you.
And you.
If it wasn't for this party,
we might never have met.
How do you do?
Enchanté.
Wow.
ETHAN: Yeah, wow.
(CHUCKLES) Kids.
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
(LOUD TECHNO MUSIC PLAYS)
Wow.
- May I take this? Thank you, sir.
- Yeah.
Isn't this great?
ETHAN: Yeah.
Zooey, do me a favor.
Try and use your best
judgment with Hugh tonight.
Cheers.
You're working again!
Yeah. There's a problem here.
That's why you came back to Paris?
No. I came back to see you and Zooey.
TINA: It was all a lie.
You promised you'd keep
your work away from us.
- You're probably not even sick.
- It's not a lie, Tina.
Right now I don't
have the time to explain.
(TINA WHIMPERS)
- How many guys do we have?
- (MUTTERS)
The police will be here
in ten minutes.
- You all right?
- No.
No, I'm not so good.
I've gotta go...
Ifwe go now, there is enough time.
OK. This party's over.
- You used us both!
- No, I would never do that.
I'll get my funds, bring everyone in.
Make sure the street's blocked.
At least have the decency
to look at me.
Kill him.
It's just bad luck.
(SCOFFS)
You're sick, Ethan.
Wow, this is unbelievable.
Yeah. I know. It's crazy.
I'm gonna be sick.
Come with me.
- (BONES CRACK)
- (YELPS)
(SCREAMS)
Did you scratch yourself?
No, please don't go.
Come home with me.
Just leave it to someone else.
Just please stay here.
- Zooey!
- What?
Get down!
(BEEPS)
You hear me in there?
I'm sending you down.
(GROANING)
(SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
(GRUNTING)
(HEARTBEATS)
Oh, shit.
(CLANKING)
(GRUNTING)
WheeI's turning.
No, stay, you fuckers!
Don't!
(ERRATIC HEARTBEATS)
I gotta...
Don't.
I wouldn't mind killing you.
You scared a lot of people up there.
This is my daughter's party.
Yes.
(MUTTERS)
Yes, come on.
Viv.
Oh, my God.
Am I in hell?
So that's what it looks like
to you, Ethan.
- (CHUCKLES)
- Figures.
- Finish it.
- What?
You'll do what I tell you to.
- No.
- Finish it.
I passed my quota, Vivi.
Ethan...
Jesus Christ!
- Are you really done working for them?
- (GIGGLING)
VIVI: A killer is a killer.
He'll never change.
I know I haven't done right by you and Zooey.
VIVI: Kill him.
I should've left a long time ago.
- What about your daughter?
- I wasn't there.
Do it.
What kind of kid
doesn't know how to ride a bike?
The kind of kid who never had
a father to teach her.
- Ethan.
- Ethan!
Do it!
ZOOEY: Promise you'll never
lie to me again.
VIVI: You have no choice.
I don't think so.
The wife wants me to give it up.
(SIRENS APPROACHING)
(WAVES CRASHING)
(SEAGULL CRIES)
TINA: Can I talk to her?
ETHAN: No, she's down on the beach
right now throwing rocks.
- TINA: What?
- ETHAN: Yeah, we're...
We're taking a break
from each other right now.
At least she's not throwing them at me.
TINA: Is everything all right?
Yeah, it's been all right.
There's been good and bad days.
She said things, I've said things.
There's been some tears,
but the week overall's
been really worth it.
Hey.
These are some presents
from me and, um...
...a package that was
dropped at the house.
I can hear your car running.
Are you gonna go back?
I love you, Tina.
Just not enough to quit.
I think you're wrong,
but I understand.
If I could say one word to you
to change your mind,
would you give me that chance?
This isn't a game.
We don't have to stay in the same room,
we don't have to sleep together,
that's not what I'm asking.
If that becomes important,
you'll be the one to decide.
I'll hear the music, and then I'll know.
And if I never hear it...
I've already gotten more than I deserve.
I just wanna hang out as long as I can
with my daughter and my wife.
- What's the word?
- What?
What's the one word
to make me change my mind?
It's, uh... it's Christmas.
(CHUCKLES)
That's two, Ethan.
- Hey, Mom!
- Hi, sweetie.
I'm so glad you came!
Come on, let's go inside.
Dad's gonna make us hot cocoa.
Come on.
(♪ THE TEMPER TRAP: "SWEET DISPOSITION")
Is Dad a badass?
Well, he's, um...
He's done some things.
You think Dad's gonna stick around?
As long as he can, sweetheart.
He loves you so much.